International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Records 5010
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Records
1952-1967
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
International Confederation of Free Trade Unions
5010
8 cubic feet
8 linear ft.
Records.
Subject files of the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions.
3111758
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, October 12, 2004
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 20, 2016
Scope and Contents
This collection consists of subject files maintained by the International Confederation of Free Trade Unions. In addition to files on specific countries, this collection contains issues of the ICFTU Information Bulletin, International Trade Union News, and other periodicals, pamphlets, and reprints.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5272: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Asian Regional Organization Records 5272 mf: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Records on Microfilm 6288 MB: John P. Windmuller Collection of ICFTU Memorabilia 5010: International Confederation of Free Trade Unions Records 5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
International labor activities.
3111758
- Africa (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Africa (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Africa (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Africa - Econ. Cond. (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Africa Boycott (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Algeria (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Algeria (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Algeria (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Argentina (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Asia (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Austria (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Baltic States (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Bolivia (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Brazil (Box 1, Folder 14)
- British Guiana (Box 1, Folder 15)
- British Honduras (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Bulgaria (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Burma (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Canada (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Caribbean Area (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Chili (Box 1, Folder 21)
- China (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Columbia (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Congo (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Costa Rica (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Cuba (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Cyprus (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Cyprus (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Cyprus (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Czechoslovakia (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Czechoslovakia (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Czechoslovakia (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Denmark (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Dominican Republic (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Dutch West Indies (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Egypt (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Egypt (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Egypt (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Finland (Box 2, Folder 4)
- France (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Germany (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Ghana (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Ghana (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Great Britain (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Greece (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Guatemala (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Guinea (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Haiti (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Honduras (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Hong Kong (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Hungary (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Hungary - Revolution, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Scope and Contents
  Autumn 1956
- Hungary - U.N. Action, 1956-1957 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 19)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 20)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 21)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 22)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 23)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 24)
- National Republic of Free Hungary (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Iceland (Box 2, Folder 26)
- India (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Indochina (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Indonesia (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Iran (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Iran (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Israel (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Italy (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Italian Somalia (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Jamaica (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Japan (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Japan (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Japan (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Jordan (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Mideast Trip (Box 3, Folder 8)
  cards and addresses
- Sugar Workers Congress, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Syria (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Oil and USSR Bustani (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 1960 Annuals - Duplicate articles (Box 3, Folder 12)
- The Christian Science Monitor, 1954-1962 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  12/23/54 - 9/26/62
- ICFTU Documents and Message (Box 3, Folder 14)
- ICFTU Articles by Arnold Beichman, 1952-1954 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Articles, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Articles, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Articles, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Articles, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Articles, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Articles - Beichman (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Mr. Beichman's Various Articles (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Carbon Copies of Beichman (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Africa (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Berlin (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Burma (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Burma (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Ceylon (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Cyprus (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Japan (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Kenya (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Tearsheets - Mid-East (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Beichman Articles - Mid-East (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Pakistan (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Singapore - India - Brussels - Cyprus - Malaya - Okinawa- Hong Kong (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Tanganyika (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Thailand (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Tokyo (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Uganda (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Viet Nam (Box 4, Folder 26)
- New Clippings (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Information Bulletin, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Information Bulletin, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Information Bulletin, 1958-1959 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- News Service ICFTU Brussels, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Information Bulletin, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Information Bulletin, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- International News, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- International Trade Union News, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- International Trade Union News, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- International Trade Union News, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Bulletin, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- International Trade Union News, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- International Trade Union News, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  French
- ICFTU Bulletin, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- International Trade Union News, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- International Trade Union News, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- International Trade Union News, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Bulletin, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Circulars, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Features, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Information, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Bulletin, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Bulletin, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  French and English
- Circulars, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Circulars (cont'd), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Circulars (cont'd), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Features, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Women's News, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Circulars, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Circulars, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Features, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Features, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Features, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- ICFTU, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- ICFTU, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Women's Int'l. Democratic Federation and Trade Union Consultative Council (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Newspaper Clippings personal (Box 7, Folder 2)
- "0" Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Labor History (Box 7, Folder 4)
- World Goodwill (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Buying and Selling Airplanes (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Democracy Under Fire (Box 7, Folder 7)
- 1962 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- U.S. Rebuff (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Labor and Unions (Box 7, Folder 10)
- World Assoc. of World Federalists (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Address to United Nations and Labor Material Labor Problems (Box 7, Folder 12)
- The Financial Times (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Burelle's News Clippings (Box 7, Folder 14)
  China and Africa
- Burelle's News Clippings (Box 7, Folder 15)
- News Clippings and Labor Information Photocopys and New Clippings - U.S. Aid Communism and econ. Stability (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Labor and Labor Unions (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Economics (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Trade Unions (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Articles, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  Summer 1963
- Trade Unions (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Labor Unions (Box 7, Folder 22)
- ICFTU Proposed French Labor College (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Labor Unions Foreign Policy (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Miscellaneous - pamphlets, reprints, etc. (Box 8, Folder All)